Part of renting a tuxedo is also having the proper footwear.
It's not unusual to have people wear their own shoes if they want to, I always think it's best to rent a shoe to go with the tuxedo you picked.
You're spending a lot of money for that tuxedo, you don't want a pair of shoes that distracts from that overall tuxedo look.
There's a lot of ways you can go on tuxedos, every tuxedo will have different styles of shoes.
There's always just the plain flat front tuxedo, high gloss.
That's a classic way to go, you'll always find that in any tuxedo place you go to and that's the good way to go.
But, it's not unusual to do some different looks.
This is a cap toe shoe.
So you can do cap toe, wing tip, there's a lot of different options on that.
Some people don't like that shiny, glossy look, kind of plastic look.
Sometimes you can buy a shoe that's a little more of a dull finish.
There's no right or wrong way to go, it's just kind of personal taste.
Popular over the last couple years has been more of a square toe, I think fashion's changing on that a little bit and going more with a point toe.
So that another thing to be aware of, that fashions change.
That's why I say maybe go conservative, that's always going to look good.
This you might at a few years down the road and say, gee that's kind of a square toe, I wish we had done something a little more up to date.
So, go conservative when in doubt.